From this point in the lesson,
从课程的这部分开始
you're going to use a Linux environment with
你将使用 Linux 环境编写 Python 脚本
Python scripts rather than a Jupyter notebook.
而不再使用 Jupyter Notebook
Jupyter notebooks are great for data science,
Jupyter Notebook 对数据科学来说是非常棒的应用
but they're not necessarily the best tool for writing modular software.
但并不是编写模块化软件的最好工具
In the next section,
在下一部分中
you'll see a classroom workspace like this one containing the code I'm about to show you.
你将会看到像这样的教室 workspace 包含了我即将介绍的代码
On the left-hand side,
左手边
you'll see a list of directories that you can access.
是可供访问的文件夹列表
Each section in the rest of the lesson has its own folder.
课程接下来的每个部分都有其对应的文件夹
This part of the lesson is discussing the modularized code folder.
课程这一部分对应的是 2_modularized_code 文件夹
Let's talk about how to modularize the Distribution
我们将讨论如何将刚才编写的 Distribution
and Gaussian classes with which you've just been working.
和 Gaussian 类的代码模块化
In Python, a module is a single Python file that contains a collection of functions,
Python 中 模块就是指一个单独的 Python 文件 其中包含一些函数
classes, and or global variables.
类 或者全局变量等
They're called modules because well, they're modular.
它们被称为模块 因为它们是模块化的
Meaning that you can reuse these files in different applications.
意味着你可以在不同的应用中重复使用这些文件
A package is essentially a collection of modules placed into a directory.
软件包本质上是放在一个目录中的模块集合
If I double-click the folder containing the modularized code,
如果我双击打开包含模块化代码的文件夹
there are three files.
可以看到其中有三个文件
But these two are the most important, Gaussiandistribution.py and Generaldistribution.py.
这两个是最重要的 Gaussiandistribution.py 和 Generaldistribution.py
These files contain the same code from the section on inheritance.
这些文件中包含了与继承那节课中相同的代码
This folder isn't quite officially a package yet,
这个文件夹目前还不是一个正式的软件包
but putting these files into the same folder is the first step to making a package.
但是将这些文件放在一个文件夹中 是构建软件包的第一步
Opening the Generaldistribution.py file,
打开 Generaldistribution.py 文件
the Distribution class code is the same as it was in the Jupyter notebook.
Distribution 类的代码与 Jupyter Notebook 中的一样
Opening the Gaussiandistribution.py file,
打开 Gaussiandistribution.py 文件
you can see that it contains the Gaussian class.
你可以看到其中包含了 Gaussian 类
The code here is almost the same as the code from the Jupyter notebook.
这里的代码与 Jupyter Notebook 几乎完全相同
However, notice that the Gaussian distribution file imports the Distribution class.
不过 可以注意到 Gaussiandistribution 文件中导入了 Distribution 类
This line says, go into the Generaldistribution.py file,
这行代码告诉 Python 进入 Generaldistribution.py 文件
and give me access to the Distribution class.
获得 Distribution 类的访问权限
I want to point out that you can also use the same syntax
这里要提示一下 使用相同的语法
to import a function from a module not just a class.
不仅可以导入模块中的类 还可以导入模块中的函数
But for this lesson, we are focusing on object-oriented programming.
不过在这门课中 我们集中探讨面向对象编程
So, I coded everything inside a class.
所以我的代码都是导入类
How can I actually use this Gaussian distribution module in a Python application?
我该如何在 Python 应用中实际使用 Gaussiandistribution 模块呢?
You can see an example in the example code.py file.
你可以在 example_code.py 文件中看到一个示例
This file imports the Gaussian class,
这个文件导入了 Gaussian 类
and then instantiates a Gaussian object.
然后实例化了一个 Gaussian 对象
Note as well that my example code file and the
另外还要注意 我的 example_code 文件和
Gaussiandistribution.py file are in the same directory.
Gaussiandistribution.py 文件在同一目录中
You'll see later in the lesson that packages and applications do not need to
你将在稍后的课程看到 只要 Python 知道在哪里查找软件包
be in the same directory as long as Python knows where to look for a package.
就不需要将软件包和应用程序放在同一目录中
Next, I'm going to open a terminal window and run the example_code.py file.
接下来 我将打开一个终端窗口运行 example_code.py 文件
If you're not familiar with using the terminal,
如果你对终端操作不熟悉
don't worry too much.
不用太过担心
Each section of this lesson comes with
课程每一部分都会有一个说明文件
an instruction file discussing how to run commands in the terminal.
说明如何在终端中运行命令
Typing Python2_modularized_code/example_
输入 python 2_modularized_code/example_code.py
code.py and hitting enter,
然后点击回车
runs the Python module, example_code.py.
运行这个 Python 模块 example_code.py
This code prints out the mean of
代码打印出
the instantiated Gaussian distribution object, which is 22.
实例化高斯分布对象的均值 22
In the next section,
在下一部分
you'll have the chance to look at this code in more detail.
你将有机会深入了解这些代码